Parents Program Records UA191
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Parents Program Records
1995 -- 2009
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
University Advancement Division
UA191
6 Linear Feet 5 boxes
The collection contains photographs, publications, and documentation concerning the Parents Program.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into one series: Unprocessed accessions.
Custodial History
This collection needs to be accessed in conjunction with the Division of University Advancement records.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research. This collection may require review before it is available for use. Please contact DCA for further details.
Scope and Contents
The collection contains photographs, publications, and documentation concerning the Parents Program.
Biographical / Historical
The Parents Program connects students' families with the Tufts community through the encouragement of philanthropy and participation in leadership activities and events. Events for Tufts parents are held on campus as well around the United States and internationally. One of the major components of the Parents Program is the Parents Leadership Council (PLC), where parents can act as ambassadors and leadership donors for the university, motivating others to make philanthropic gifts. Members of the PLC also have opportunities to give feedback on special projects and activities.
Another hallmark event for the Parents Program is Parents and Family Weekend, traditionally held each October on the Medford campus. Parents and family members of Tufts students are invited to come meet faculty, staff, and other students, as well as attend lectures, career-coaching sessions, sporting events, and performances.
Advancement
- Additional accessions, 1995 -- 2008; UA191.001
  - Parents Weekend Photos, 1995 -- 2002; UA191-001 (Box data_value_missing_e508426596e9359712dc14b43db8a26b, Box 1)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Open for research.
  - Parents Weekend Photos, 1997 -- 1998; UA191-002 (Box 1, Box 2)
  - Parents Weekend Photos and publications, 2000 -- 2009; UA191-003 (Box 1, Box 3)
  - Parents Weekend Photos, 1996 -- 2008; UA191-004 (Box data_value_missing_f7066f55d246568708c0403d7721e26b, Box 4)
  - Parents Weekend Photos, 1996 -- 2008; UA191-005 (Box data_value_missing_1d170c13f38a66375b0949a02137b0ef, Box 5)
  - Parents Weekend Photos, 1996 -- 2008; UA191-006 (Box data_value_missing_1d170c13f38a66375b0949a02137b0ef, Box 6)
  - Parents Weekend Photos, 1996 -- 2008; UA191-007 (Box data_value_missing_f7066f55d246568708c0403d7721e26b, Box 7)
  - Parents Weekend Photos, 1996 -- 2008; UA191-008 (Box data_value_missing_1d170c13f38a66375b0949a02137b0ef, Box 8)
  - Parents Weekend Photos, 1996 -- 2008; UA191-009 (Box data_value_missing_435a4996dd1c61243a111d800cb39cf1, Box 9)